

# Seoul, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-5577-5814 | ■ newinh90@gmail.com | ♣ newinh.me | □ newinh | 🗟 newinh | 🛅 newinh

## **Summary** \_

1+ year experience in back-end development. Experienced embedded, Android, iOS development as a beginner, recently worked on project related to collecting data in fashion AI company.

Open culture of IT industry was so impressive that I started developmenting software. As I got help and inspired, I want to be a engineer who can help. Main skills are Python, flask, MySQL now, but i'm ready to challenge other technical skills and accomplish projects.

### Skills

**Programming** Python

**Frameworks** Flask, Scrapy, pandas **Infrastructures** AWS, Docker, MySQL

**Languages** Korea(native), English(Business)

# Work Experience

Kasa Korea Co., Ltd. Seoul, S.Korea

Back-end Engineer Jul. 2019 -

Omnious. Co., Ltd. Seoul, S.Korea

Back-end Engineer Nov. 2017 - Jul. 2019

#### **Labeling Tool**

- · Maintained back-end of in-house web application having 50+ active users for collecting fashion data to train AI model.
  - Docker, CircleCI, Rancher, AWS(EC2, S3, RDS)
- $\bullet \ \ {\tt Designed \,RESTful \, HTTP \, API, \, developed \, server \, serving \, them. \, \, {\tt Documented \, API \, specification \, for \, communication.} \\$ 
  - flask, NGINX, uWSGI, Swagger
- Established relation of domain model, designed database schema.
  - MySQL
- Built HTTP access logging system and pipeline to store it.
  - fluntd, fluent-bit
- Introduced unit testing, style guide of codebase.
  - flake8, pytest

#### **Data Extraction & Transformation**

- Extracted collected data to train AI model and pre-processed in a form that is easy to train.
- Automated process from data extraction to data processing, developed CLI tool to access automated data transfer system.
- pandas, Celery

#### Crawler

- Implemented 20+ web crawlers for collecting fashion images, developed a scheduling tool for management.
- Built serverless pipeline that stores crawled data in a storage.
- Scrapy, ScrapingHub, Zappa, AWS(SNS, SQS, Labmda)

**LayGen Inc.** Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Aug. 2017 - Sep. 2017

- Participated to manufactoring operating module for a prototype of 3D printer and developed software control the module.
- Developed GUI so that hardware engineer can test controling each part of 3D printer.
- Python, PyQT, Rasberry Pi, Arduino

LINE Corp. Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea, S.Korea

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Apr. 2017 - May. 2017

- Prototyped iOS application "Targeted Video" emphasizing object user want in video.
- Used technique of contour extraction, image segmentation and stabilization.
- Implemented video editing function that cuts or pastes object user selected.
- Swift, OpenCV

**UXEnterprise**Seoul, S.Korea

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Aug. 2016 - Sep. 2016

- Prototyped Android application viewing Female biorhythm.
- Implemented connection with a measuring device using Bluetooth.
- Java, Android

## **Education**

### **BoostCamp, Connect Foundation education program**

Seoul, S.Korea

iOS Course

Jan. 2017 - Feb. 2017

- Developed iOS Application, "Color to Sound, Sound to Color! ChromaTone"
  - https://github.com/newinh/ChromaTone

Konkuk University Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN ELECTRONICS

Mar. 2009 - Feb. 2016

• Graduation piece, "IOT Door Lock using Wireless Home Router & Android Device"